en:
  static_pages:
    home:
      header: "Exam System"
      title: "Home"
      content: "This is the home page for the exam system"
      sign_in: "Sign in"
      welcome: "Welcome to Exam System"
  shared:
    error_messages:
      form: "The form contains"
    user_info:
      view_profile: "View my profile"
  sessions:
    new:
      header: "Login"
      title: "Login"
      password: "Password"
      password_form: "*******"
      login: "Login"
      logged_in: "You are logged in."
      remember_me: "Remember me"
      email: "Email"
      forgot_pass: "Forgot Password"
  layouts:
    header:
      title_home: "Home"
      user: "User"
      logout: "Logout"
      login: "Login"
      exam_system: "Exam system"
      account: "Account"
      subject: "Subjects"
      dif: "Other"
      question: "Questions"
      settings: "Settings"
      list_exam: "List exam"
      logout: "Logout"
      login: "Login"
      profile: "Profile"
      settings: "Settings"
      en: "English"
      vi: "Vietnamese"
    application:
      logout: "Sign Out"
      profile: "My Profile"
      setting: "Setting"
    logout_modal:
      leave: "Ready to Leave?"
      logout_mess: "Select 'Logout' below if you are ready to end your current session."
      cancel: "Cancel"
      logout: "Logout"
    sidebar:
      title: "EXAM SYSTEM"
      dashboard: "Report"
      languages: "Languages"
      messages: "Messages"
      admin: "Admin"
      account_mana: "Accounts management"
      user: "Users"
      list_account: "List accounts"
      new_account: "New account"
      nomal_user: "User"
      profile: "Profile"
      view_profile: "View profile"
      edit_profile: "Edit profile"
      main: "Main"
      subject_mana: "Subjects management"
      subject: "Subjects"
      new_subject: "New Subject"
      topics: "Topics"
      list_subject: "List subjects"
      topic_mana: "Topics management"
      list_topic: "List Topics"
      new_topic: "Add Topic"
      new_exam: "Add Exam"
      list_exam: "List exams"
      channels: "Channels"
    topbar:
      languages: "Languages"
      en: " English"
      vi: " Vietnamese"
      messages: "Messages"
      profile: "Profile"
      topics: "Topics"
      logout: "Logout"
      search_for: "Search for..."
      search: "Search"
  static_pages:
    dashboard:
      pie_chart: "The graph shows the ratio of the number of exams of the subjects"
      pie_chart_1: "The graph shows the ratio of points"
      column_chart: "Graph showing average test scores across subjects"
  users:
    edit:
      header: "Editing User"
      conf: "Password Confirmation"
      name: "Name"
      email: "Email"
      password: "Password"
      title: "Edit profile"
      edit_user: "Edit profile"
      button_text: "Edit"
    new:
      header: "Add a new user"
      title: "Add a new user"
      buttontext: "Create a new account"
      create_user: "Create a new account"
    form:
      name: "Name"
      email: "Email"
      role: "Role"
      pass: "Password"
      conf: "Password confirm"
    error:
      error: "error prohibited this user from being saved:"
    show:
      id: "Id: "
      name: "Name: "
      role: "Role: "
      email: "Email: "
      table: "Profile"
      add_user: "add user"
    index:
      title: "List users"
      create: "Add a new user"
      no_: "No"
      name: "Name"
      email: "Email"
      role: "Role"
      status: "Status"
      updated_or_deleted: "Updated/Deleted at"
      action: "Action"
    create:
      save_user: "Successfully, added new user"
      fail_save: "Failed, can't add new user"
  subjects:
    new:
      title: "Add a new subject"
      header: "New subject"
      button_text: "Create a new subject"
      create_subject: "Add a new subject"
    form:
      name: "Name: "
      description: "Description: "
      user_create_id: "User create: %{name}"
    show:
      user_name: "User created: "
    index:
      title: "Subjects"
      header: "Subjects"
      list_question: "Questions"
      list_exam: "Exams"
      table: "List subjects"
      id: "ID: "
      user: "User create: "
      search: "Search"
      des: "Describe"
      del: "Delete"
      new: "+New"
      title: "List subjects"
      create: "Add a new subject"
      no_: "No"
      name: "Name"
      description: "Description"
      user_name: "User name"
      topic_name: "Topics"
      action: "Action"
    search:
      user: "User"
      all: "All"
      name: "Name of subject"
      input_name: "Input name"
      description: "Description"
      input_description: "Input description"
      start_date: "Created at to: "
      end_date: "Created at from: "
      search: "Search"
      reset: "Cancel"
    subject:
      delete: "Delete"
      sure: "delete?"
  questions:
    index:
      title: "Questions"
      header: "Questions"
      add_question: "+new question"
      create: "Create new question"
    new:
      title: "Question"
      button_text: "Create a new question"
      header: "Questions"
    edit:
      title: "Edit question"
      button_text: "Edit"
      text: "Edit answer and content"
    questions:
      user_create: "User name: %{name}"
      content: "Content:"
      delete: "Delete"
      sure: "Sure?"
      edit_question: "Edit question"
      answer: "Answer:"
      user: "User create:"
      ans: "Answer: "
    form:
      answer: "Answer:"
      content: "Content"
      add_answer: "Add new answer"
      add_ans: "Add new answer"
      level: "Level"
      question_type: "Question type"
      topic: "Topic"
    answer_fields:
      answer: "Answer: "
      content: "Content"
      check: "Answer is right or wrong"
      remove_answer: "Remove answer"
    create:
      message_success: "Create question success"
  exams:
    exam:
      question: "Question"
      subject: "Subject"
      sure: "Delete?"
      delete: "Delete"
    form:
      question: "Question"
      add_questions_exam: "Add a question"
    questions_exam_fields:
      score: "Score"
      remove_question: "Remove question"
    index:
      title: "Exam"
      add_exams: "Add a new exam"
      header: "Exam"
      id: "ID"
      sub: "Subject"
      num: "Sum questions"
      del: "Delete"
      user: "User create"
      table: "List exam"
      create: "Add a new exam"
      id: "ID"
      subject: "Subject"
      topic_name: "Topic"
      user_name: "User"
      time: "Time do exam"
      action: "Action"

    new:
      title: "New Exam"
      button_text: "Create a new exam"
      header: "New Exam"
    show:
      questions: "Count questions: "
      code: "Code exam"
      time_remaining: "Time remaining"
      title: "Exam"
      submit: "Submit"
      time: "Time do exam"
      score: "Score: %{score}"
      right: "Right: %{score}/%{count}"
      question: "Question %{index}: %{des}"
      user: "User do exam: %{user}"
      button_export_pdf: "Download as pdf"
      title: "Exam"
    question:
      question: "Question %{index}: %{des}"
    search:
      topic: "Topic"
      all: "All"
      user: "User"
      start_date: "Created at to: "
      end_date: "Created at from: "
      search: "Search"
      reset: "Cancel"
  questions_exams:
    questions_exams:
      code_exam: "Code exam"
      subject_exam: "Subject exam"
      count_questions: "Count questions"
      question: "Question"
      content: "Content"
      answer: "Answer"
      delete: "Delete"
      edit_question: "Edit question"
      score: "Score"
      sure: "Delete?"
    show:
      header: "Questions of exam"
      questions: "Questions"
  topics:
    index:
      no_: "NO"
      name: "Name of topic"
      des: "Description"
      duration: "Duration(minutes)"
      user_name: "User name"
      subject_name: "Subject"
      updated_or_deleted: "Time updated/deleted"
      action: "Actions"
      title: "List exams"
      create: "Create new exam"
      start: "Start"
    new:
      button_text: "Create a new topic"
      create_topic: "Create a new topic"
    form:
      description: "Description"
      name: "Name"
      subject: "Subject"
      duration: "Duration(minutes)"
    search:
      user: "User create"
      subject: "Subject"
      all: "All"
      description: "Description"
      input_description: "Input description"
      start_date: "Created at to: "
      end_date: "Created at from: "
      search: "Search"
      reset: "Cancel"
  pagy:
    nav:
      next: "Next ›"
      prev: "‹ Prev"
      gap: "…"
  success_exam: "Success"
  fail_exam: "Fail"
  exam_not_found: "Exam not found"
  deleted_exam: "Deleted"
  fail_delete_exam: "Cant delete this exam"
  success_question: "Successful"
  fail_question: "create failed"
  deleted_question: "deleted"
  question_not_found: "Quesion not found"
  fail: "Create user fail"
  deleted: "Deleted"
  fail_delete: "Can not delete"
  user_not_found: "user not found"
  subject_not_found: "subject not found"
  success: "Create new user successfully"
  please_login: "Please login"
  danger: "Invalid  email/ password combination"
  base_title: "Exam System"
  login_success: "Logged in successfully"
  error: "errors"
  success_subject: "Create a new subject successfully"
  fail_subject: "Create subject fail"
  updated_successfully: "Update successfully"
  updated_failed: "Update failed"
  submit_success: "Submit success"
  submit_fail: "Submit fail"
  success_topic: "Submit success"
  success_message: "success"
